"They're all at that party without me…
"他们都在那个派对上，就我没去……
I've got such bad FOMO."
我得了严重的错失恐惧症。"
The fear of missing out, or 'FOMO', is what you might feel when you aren't present when something exciting or enjoyable is happening.
错失恐惧症指的是当你不在某个令人兴奋或愉快的场合时所感受到的焦虑。
This anxiety is rife in the age of social media, where we're exposed to an avalanche of updates about other people's holidays, social events and achievements.
这种焦虑在社交媒体时代十分普遍，我们被铺天盖地的关于他人假期、社交活动和成就的更新内容所淹没。
Many find themselves comparing their lives to others', forgetting that social media is often a smokescreen, where we only see the highlight reel and a veneer of perfection.
许多人发现自己将自己的生活与别人的相比较，忘记了社交媒体往往是一种烟幕弹，在那里我们只能看到精彩片段集锦和完美的表象。
As an antidote to this constant pressure, many are embracing 'JOMO' – the joy of missing out.
作为对这种持续压力的解药，许多人开始接受"错失的快乐"。
According to Svend Brinkmann, author of 'The Joy of Missing Out: The Art of Self-Restraint in an Age of Excess', the difference is that where FOMO gets us to worry about things outside of the present moment, JOMO brings us back to the here and now, encouraging us to enjoy life offline with people we truly care about.
根据《错失的快乐：过剩时代的自我克制艺术》一书的作者斯文德·布林克曼的说法，区别在于，错失恐惧症让我们担心当下之外的事情，而错失的快乐则把我们带回此时此地，鼓励我们与真正在乎的人在线下享受生活。
Embracing JOMO means switching off outside noise and focusing on what really brings us happiness.
接受错失的快乐意味着关掉外界的噪音，专注于真正给我们带来快乐的事情。
So, how can we stop FOMO from rearing its ugly head?
那么，我们如何才能阻止错失恐惧症的出现呢？
In her book 'The Joy of Missing Out: Live More by Doing Less', Tanya Dalton suggests making a list of activities that bring you joy and displaying them somewhere obvious to remind you to include them in your day.
在她的《错失的快乐：做得更少，活得更好》一书中，坦尼娅·道尔顿建议列出能给你带来快乐的活动清单，并把它们放在显眼的地方，提醒自己把它们安排到当天行程当中。
She also suggests a regular digital detox and carving out time for self-care, whether that's a warm bath, a solo nature walk or your favourite movie.
她还建议定期进行数字排毒，并腾出时间关注和照料自己，无论是洗个热水澡、独自在大自然中散步，还是看你最喜欢的电影。
Kristen Fuller, a physician and mental health writer, says it's about being intentional with your time.
医生兼心理健康作家克里斯汀·富勒说，关键在于有意识地使用你的时间。
This involves scheduling activities which are important to you and practising saying "no" to people if you feel like their request will have a negative impact on you.
这包括安排对你重要的活动，并练习在觉得别人的要求会对你有负面影响时对他们说"不"。
A 2019 article by Ana Jorge, published in Social Media + Society looked into the experiences of people who purposefully disconnect from social media.
安娜·豪尔赫2019年发表在《社交媒体+社会》上的一篇文章研究了那些有意断开社交媒体连接的人的经历。
Some of them felt they were living more mindfully, and that the disconnection allowed them to be more creative and productive.
他们中的一些人觉得自己生活得更专注，而这种断联让他们更有创造力和生产力。
About JOMO, one participant told researchers, "I don't have to be everywhere, I don't have to be with everyone and I don't have to know everything."
关于错失的快乐，一位参与者告诉研究人员："我不必无处不在，不必与所有人在一起，也不必什么都知道。"
Perhaps it's time to unplug and try living life in the slow lane.
也许是时候拔掉电源，试着过慢节奏的生活了。